// import 'package:sight_reading_app/lessons_and_quizzes/question_list.dart';
//
// /// List of questions for lesson 6.
// ///
// /// Teaches how to read higher notes than the ones taught in previous lessons.
//
// final QuestionList lessonSixQuestions =
//     QuestionList(lessonID: 6, questionList: [
//   ///Tutorial
//   // Question(
//   //   note: Note(name: 'C5', duration: 4),
//   //   clef: Clef.treble,
//   //   question:
//   //       'We are going to read notes higher than usual. The higher the note on on 5 line staff, the higher the pitch. Tap C for this note',
//   //   correctAnswer: 'C',
//   // ),
//   // Question(
//   //   note: Note(name: 'D5', duration: 4),
//   //   clef: Clef.treble,
//   //   question:
//   //       'Notice that this note is higher than C in the previous question. Press D in the option box.',
//   //   correctAnswer: 'D',
//   // ),
//   // Question(
//   //   note: Note(name: 'G3', duration: 4),
//   //   clef: Clef.bass,
//   //   question:
//   //       'The same goes for notes in Base clef. Do you remember this note? This is G in Bass Clef. Press G in the option box.',
//   //   correctAnswer: 'G',
//   // ),
//   // Question(
//   //   note: Note(name: 'A3', duration: 4),
//   //   clef: Clef.bass,
//   //   question:
//   //       'This note is on the line above G in the previous question. Now press A in the option box.',
//   //   correctAnswer: 'A',
//   // ),
//   //
//   // ///Start questions
//   // Question(
//   //   note: Note(name: 'B4', duration: 4),
//   //   clef: Clef.treble,
//   //   question:
//   //       'Great Job. All notes will repeat the pattern C-D-E-F-G-A-B before going back to C as you go higher up on the musical staff. For an actual keyboard/piano, you will go further to the right. Try answering the rest of the questions without help. What note is this?',
//   //   correctAnswer: 'B',
//   // ),
//   // Question(
//   //   note: Note(name: 'C5', duration: 4),
//   //   clef: Clef.treble,
//   //   question: 'What note is this?',
//   //   correctAnswer: 'C',
//   // ),
//   // Question(
//   //   note: Note(name: 'D5', duration: 4),
//   //   clef: Clef.treble,
//   //   question: 'What note is this?',
//   //   correctAnswer: 'D',
//   // ),
//   // Question(
//   //   note: Note(name: 'G3', duration: 4),
//   //   clef: Clef.bass,
//   //   question: 'What note is this?',
//   //   correctAnswer: 'G',
//   // ),
//   // Question(
//   //   note: Note(name: 'A3', duration: 4),
//   //   clef: Clef.bass,
//   //   question: 'What note is this?',
//   //   correctAnswer: 'A',
//   // ),
//   // Question(
//   //   note: Note(name: 'B3', duration: 4),
//   //   clef: Clef.bass,
//   //   question: 'What note is this?',
//   //   correctAnswer: 'B',
//   // ),
//   // Question(
//   //   note: Note(name: 'E5', duration: 4),
//   //   clef: Clef.treble,
//   //   question: 'What note is this?',
//   //   correctAnswer: 'E',
//   // ),
//   // Question(
//   //   note: Note(name: 'A4', duration: 4),
//   //   clef: Clef.treble,
//   //   question: 'What note is this?',
//   //   correctAnswer: 'A',
//   // ),
//   // Question(
//   //   note: Note(name: 'C5', duration: 4),
//   //   clef: Clef.treble,
//   //   question: 'What note is this?',
//   //   correctAnswer: 'C',
//   // ),
//   // Question(
//   //   note: Note(name: 'D5', duration: 4),
//   //   clef: Clef.treble,
//   //   question: 'What note is this?',
//   //   correctAnswer: 'D',
//   // ),
//   // Question(
//   //   note: Note(name: 'G3', duration: 4),
//   //   clef: Clef.bass,
//   //   question: 'What note is this?',
//   //   correctAnswer: 'G',
//   // ),
//   // Question(
//   //   note: Note(name: 'B3', duration: 4),
//   //   clef: Clef.bass,
//   //   question: 'What note is this?',
//   //   correctAnswer: 'B',
//   // ),
//   // Question(
//   //   note: Note(name: 'F3', duration: 4),
//   //   clef: Clef.bass,
//   //   question: 'What note is this?',
//   //   correctAnswer: 'F',
//   // ),
//   // Question(
//   //   note: Note(name: 'A3', duration: 4),
//   //   clef: Clef.bass,
//   //   question: 'What note is this?',
//   //   correctAnswer: 'A',
//   // ),
// ]);
